So here we are, Harajuku Smile!
Yay!
Let's get it!
Agekeero!
Let's pick a crepe!
We can finally eat!
You like it?
I love it!
I like it so much that I often deliver them at home.
No way!
So much so that you order crepes for delivery?
That's amazing!
Let's eat a lot of sweet stuff already!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you allowed to stand in line?
Stop your impersonation, please.
Stop it.
You don't look like him.
We don't look alike.
Order!
I'm ordering a crepe.
I'll have the strawberry chocolate.
Yes, sir.
Moutella banana whipped cream.
Wow!
I'll have the, um...
Whipped cream and soft serve topping, please.
Oh!
And please add strawberries.
I'm sorry, but you're being too aggressive.
I'm sorry... but you can add any toppings you want.
What's with the pie?
What's that?
It's a special!
I'm glad she's happy.
Suddenly, it's a little awkward.
Why?
Why? I'm sorry. Why? Why did it have to come to this?
You're angry, Ano.
I'm mad at you.
Why?
Is it too loud? I don't know.
I don't get it.
I don't even eat weed. I don't usually eat weep.
What do you eat?
I like spicy food.
I also drink a lot.
Are you a heavy drinker?
You've been here quite a while.
It's bad.
I saw a story where you drank toilets.
I saw a story about a man who drank a lot of toilets.
I'm sure it's a thing.
I'm sure it's not a secret.
You have work to do?
Yes.
Then, Mr. Iwakura...
She's really cute.
That's true.
Why is she so cute?
She's so precious!
That's what she said.
But they made you blonde.
There was an older black gal.
One of them said to me.
"Isn't your blonde hair too much? something like that.
"Isn't your hair too blonde?
I thought so too.
There's a lot of excitement in the gal community.
It's kind of a hit with the gals.
Really?
Michyopa and Nikoru
They both sent me a message.
Hee...
They said I was cute.
You're really cute!
Of course I love your black hair.
I dyed it for work.
I'm going to dye it back eventually.
I guess you will.
It's like a trademark of yours.
I've had black hair for over 10 years since I was born.
I'm a little uncomfortable with it.
I was wearing a black wig for the Kohaku press conference.
I was already in gold, so I was like, "Which will it be, red or white?
I'm looking forward to that too.
I put it back.
Oh, here it is!
Ettela Banana!
Here you go.
Delicious!
Ettela Banana Strawberry with delicious Ettela Banana Chocolate.
Thank you.
Look at that!
Click.
I thought there was just a little bit of soft-serve ice cream in there.
But it's got a big scoop of soft serve ice cream!
Click!
That's amazing!
You can share a little bit.
You want me to put it on, or do you want a little bit? Anna, a little bit.
I'm fine. I'm okay, too.
You're kidding!
Let's eat! Bon appétit.
Wow. Yum!
Delicious! But it's not good!
Oh no!
Oh, my God.
It's so good!
I spit it out!
Use a spoon.
Good luck with that.
Don't tell me what to do.
You're not like you used to be.
I'm Bodhi.
No, you can't.
Head.
It's definitely not good.
You've got to have it.
It's too hard to eat.
It's not hygienic.
Can we name it something like "The Three of Us"?
What?
When you first got dressed and she came out...
What did he say? Was it legendary?
The one where the three of us united under heaven on Takeshita-dori?
Unification of Japan?
Was that it?
Wow!
We're going to unite Takeshita-dori! I'm going to make it "Unification of the whole country" with an extension stick at the top.
How was it, Tabu?
I'm so glad you mentioned my name on the radio before... and I went to listen to it... and we were at an event together... and I wanted to be with you.
I was so happy to hear her name, but I went to ask her about it, and we were at an event together, and she was like, "Oh, my mother's there.
I heard it. I heard it.
She was so tired.
I'm so tired.
But I was happy.
Really?
I thought that you remembered me.
I thought that you had left a huge impression on me.
It's still with me.
Really?
I was so happy because Benshoga won the competition and I've been so grateful to him.
I was like, "Yay! I was like, "Finally, Benshoga won! Finally, Benshoga won! I thought.
And then, when it was over, I thought, "What is that?
Oh, is that it? I lost? I thought.
That's a lie.
Benshoga won, which means I lost. I thought, "If Alemberto won, that means I lost, and I'm going to lose for another year," and I was in despair.
I felt like I was in a dream at the time, so I was like, "Wow, I'm in despair!
I've been wondering if I could be on TV like Zaree and Shinichi.
I'm wondering how I'm going to find a way.
Are you two people who get along well with each other?
Yes, they are.
After it's over...
I called them.
They said they could have a drink together.
So I called.
So we went nonstop.
I was really running.
I couldn't stop running.
It's a lyric from Chatmonchi, right?
You know, the one where he says, "I can't stop my feet from moving"?
It's like it really comes out in your head in the same way as the song.
I was so happy.
In my heart, I was going to beat squash.
Like, "I don't know if you won, but don't get carried away.
I was going to be like, "I don't know if I won, but don't get carried away," and that was my first shot.
But I don't have that anymore.
I was really surprised.
It's amazing what the human body can do.
Really?
I did get a call from Mr. Iwakura.
I was like, "I'm going anyway.
I was like, "I'll be there anyway.
Like, "I'll wait for you.
You idiot, you seriously haven't stopped.
I seriously didn't stop.
That's when he suddenly told me.
So that's what happened.
I ran for real for about 10 minutes.
Dashing.
I was so happy that the three of us had dinner together afterwards.
And then I went home and cried.
Oh, no.
I didn't say that.
I was so happy when I got home.
I couldn't hold back my tears anymore.
Mr. Kumamoto, Mr. Red Ginger said he wasn't going to be there.
I called Mr. Ito, Oswald's Mr. Ito.
I was so happy that Mr. Red Ginger won.
I didn't know there was such a long way to go.
That was a great night.
I knew you were cool and nice.
That kind of friendship...
It's a bond.
I don't have that.
I envy you.
I don't know if it's good or bad to have a bond.
It depends on the person.
But I like the fact that it's a boys' magazine.
It's like this feeling of going up.
So the music isn't a battle or anything?
But I'm glad to hear you'll be in Kohaku.
We're both happy!
I'm so happy!
I mean, I've never been in a situation like this before in my life.
Isn't it terrible to be in Kohaku in your life?
Yes, it is.
I want to hang out with Magic Mamot-san and the 4 of us.
I want to play with you because I've never met you before.
When we eat dinner, I always take a bite.
Wow!
I'd like to meet him.
I'd like to have a bite every time I eat my rice. I'd like to meet your hands.
I'll bite into it every time I eat my rice.
What are you talking about?
We don't have a comedian.
Ume chazuke (plum flavored rice with green tea) is here.
I said, "Mr. Iwakura, this ochazuke is delicious!
and Mr. Iwakura says...
and Mr. Iwakura said, "Ha ha ha ha!
No tskkomi!
The absence of a "tskkomi" (a commenter) is a permanent problem, isn't it?
And Mr. Kumamoto...
Kumamoto-san was really pissed off.
Then Tokyo is a bad place.
Kumamoto-san came to Tokyo last year.
Tokyo's a disaster.
Tokyo's geisha theater.
I'm going to fall in love with all of them.
I'm so mad!
I'm getting a soft spot.
What the hell?
Buchi kiri tsutsu
There's another one coming up.
I'm moving on.
We're moving on.
Please.
I want to look good.
This is Toppy Candy Factory Harajuku.
Toppy Candy Factory Harajuku!
Toppy Candy Factory
Cotton candy?
Cotton candy!
I'm so full!
I'm looking forward to it!
This way!
Cute and full of fun.
Oh, it's so cute!
Isn't it cute?
So colorful!
This one, too.
I wonder what this one is, too.
It says, "Welcome back, candy.
There's so much candy.
It's like this...
It looks cute.
It's cute, it looks good, and it's scary.
Are you interested in looking good?
I don't have much experience.
I'd like to take a picture like this.
I don't look good enough.
Not good enough?
Not good enough.
Seriously, we're invincible right now.
What was it again?
National Unity.
Don't forget.
We're not early.
We just decided.
Let's order.
Hello.
It's flavored.
Five different colors of cotton candy.
Each one has a different flavor.
I see.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Come here... me!
Wow, that was fast!
It's a great art, isn't it?
Add pink!
Oh!
That was fast!
What's six colors from here?
Oh, here comes orange!
Aaaaah!
It's huge!
It smells so sweet!
Wow! It's huge! It smells so sweet! Amazing!
Big!
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha!
No! It's so big!
It's huge!
Wow!
It's done!
May I? Thank you!
It's huge! Interesting!
You can't see much, can you?
It's bigger than I thought it would be!
Three of these?
I ordered three of these!
I don't think I need three!
They are huge!
We can all have one.
You're right.
Why don't we have grapes, soda, melon, and orange, and you can guess after you eat them?
Oh, there it is!
Oh, here it is!
Look, cotton candy afronts!
Ha-ha-ha!
It's a cotton candy afron!
Yay!
You heat it up, too.
A cotton candy aphron, please.
Uh, short comedy, cotton candy.
Wow, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame, wataame...
Wow, wata ame, wata ame, wata ame, wata ame.
Wow, that's good.
What's the matter?
What's wrong? Oh, my God, it's so good, I coughed.
I got cotton candy from coughing.
Cough, cough, cough.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you very much.
Is this right? Mr. Iwakura.
That's what I'm talking about. Did you like it?
It fits.
It doesn't match, does it? Just now. No matter what I think.
Oh, here he is.
Thank you.
Want some?
Let's eat.
Look, look.
Teka-san, don't you look like Watame's drills?
Watame-drills! Yuck!
It's delicious.
Yum!
Grape is good.
Yum! - Yum!
Please don't pick me up from my tongue.
Uma.
It melts right in your mouth.
A lot. But you're eating that restaurant.
Yeah, it's good.
It's delicious.
I don't know, the burpees are so...
Sweet.
Sure, but you have to eat a lot of tongue.
It's very hard to eat more!
Oh, strawberry!
Amazing! That's not the way to eat them!
What? Harajuku doesn't have that?
No way!
It's so cute! and eat a little at a time.
Don't make such a mess.
It's fine, but...
Tell me and it's totally different.
Hey!
I want to eat it for Yuuka.
You're so cute! And say...
I'm not the kind of guy who eats that much.
Moreover, there is a very popular store below this store
Strawberry Fetish also has strawberry candy!
He who controls the strawberry candy controls the plum!
Normal strawberry candy this time
Strawberry grape candy
We have three kinds of strawberry marshmallow candy.
Sorry, I didn't listen.
I knew it.
What is it?
Strawberry candy is fine.
Can I have a regular strawberry candy?
Yeah, sure.
Then marshmallows.
Okay, marshmallow. I'll have strawberry grape candy.
Strawberry grape candy!
You, a whole bunch of strawberries and marshmallows.
Strawberry candy!
Grapes are so delicious!
My stomach is really turning into a belly axis!
It must be really colorful! My stomach is really turning into a stomach!
It's so colorful, isn't it?
Delicious!
I'm curious about the grapes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
I'm sorry. I think it's like this.
Oh, it's good, it's good.
Oh, yeah.
Grapes are delicious.
Wow, they're growing so fast!
Wow!
Wow.
They're melting a little bit.
Inside?
Anochan, can the three of us get together again?
Yes, let's unite for real.
Real unification?
I'm afraid of real unification.
Kumamoto-san, please read this.
May I?
I'd like to do it myself someday.
I'd love to do your makeup someday.
The kind I usually do?
I'd like to have a bob or a black bob.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Nice? We'll unite the world that way, too.
What?
You're having too much fun in Harajuku.
I thought you weren't, but we're talking.
It's a little rude to take a picture.
That's fine.
I'm a good friend of hers.
I've never seen you this excited.
You're too excited.
You should bring me to this fun place sooner.
I don't understand.
Where do you want to go next?
Where would you like to go?
Is it the other way around?
There's so many places.
Maybe a picnic.
Maybe solve a mystery.
Riddle solving sounds nice.
Escape games.
I want to try something.
The three of us.
Let's do it.
End with a blast of heavenly music
Mr. President...
Please, we, Takeshita coworkers, end with the howl of unification of the whole country.
Yes, please!
We are Takeshita colleagues!
Unification of the whole country
Let's do it!
We'll do it!
That's right... you're so cute!